

# ABDULLAH ALMUDARHIM TECHNICAL SUPPORT

#### **COMPUTER & NETWORK**

Specialized in Computer and Information Technology from Jubail Industrial College, JIC. I have several skills in Computer and Network.I'm advance in Microsoft Windows ,Server, Active Directory(AD),Microsoft Office, Backup Program ,manage Email in Exchange Server,configure Router,Switch and access Card.

# CONTACT

- +966542240661
- modrhem1@gmail.com
  - KSA, Eastern Province

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic English



# EXPERIENCE

Al-Othman Information Technology Co. | Agu 2021 - Nov 2022

## **2022** JUNIOR TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Worked as System Administration. by Manage Active Directory and Configure Computer and Network system.

Cooperative Work in Municipality|Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

# 2021 JUNIOR TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Worked as IT Support and Network Technician During Municipality Training Work Experience.



#### **EDUCATION**

ASSOCIATE DEGREE [HIGHER DIPLOMA] OF SCIENCE: COMPUTER AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Jubail Industrial College, JIC | 2018-2021



### CERTIFICATE

- Cisco Certificate Network Associate: 200-301 (CCNA)
- Accreditation of the Council of Engineers (SCE)
- Standardized Test of English Proficiency (STEP)
- Technical Support Fundamentals (Coursera)



## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Manage User and Group in Active Directory
- Configure L3Switch, make VLAN and View STP
- Server, Router and Fire Wall Configuration
- ❖ Install and Configure Windows 7,8,10,vista
- Hardware and Software Maintenance
- DHCP, DNS, Group Policy LAN, WAN, VLAN
- Crimp RJ45, Jack Module, UTP, STP, Fiber Optic
- ❖ Backup and Restore, Clone HDD to SDD
- Virtualization Technology Hyper-V,VMWare



# PERSONAL SKILLS

Word Excel

PowerPoint Access

Outlook ERP Porgrams